http://www.blankshirts.com/custservice/privacy

PRIVACY POLICY
Last updated June 25, 2013
This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for BlankShirts.com. The statement does not include the privacy practices for partnered sites. We encourage our users who visit external sites from links within BlankShirts.com to read the privacy statements of those sites, as their privacy practices may differ from ours. The BlankShirts.com website is owned by Blank Shirts, Inc. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact us via the Customer Service Contact Form or by calling (800) 332-6576. If you prefer to write us our mailing address is below:
Blank Shirts, Inc.
1780 Forrest Way
Carson City, NV 89706
Welcome to the Blank Shirts online store. In order to make you feel comfortable and secure in our online store, Blank Shirts, Inc. has taken numerous precautions to guard your security while making purchases online. Our goal is to make you feel as comfortable shopping here as you would from our catalog or retail showrooms. For each visitor to our Web site, our Web server automatically recognizes the consumer's domain name and e-mail address (where possible).
TABLE OF CONTENTS
What personally identifiable information is being collected?
How is the information being used?
With whom do we share your information?
How do I access, update, or delete my personally identifiable information?
What information will be disclosed if required by law?
What are cookies and how do we use them?
What choices are available to you regarding the collection, use and distribution of the information and how you can correct any inaccuracies in information?
What kind of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control?
PRIVACY
What personally identifiable information is being collected?
When you visit BlankShirts.com, in order for us to provide you with the products or services that you have requested, you may be asked to provide us with personally identifiable information. For example, when you order a product, we may ask you to become a registered user of our site, during which you will be asked for your shipping and billing addresses, your e-mail address, and your credit card number or other payment-related information. If you request one of our newsletters or send an inquiry to one of our customer service representatives, we will also store a record of your request along with your e-mail address. In addition, our Web servers track various technical details about your visit, such as you computer's IP address and which pages you visited, however that information does not typically contain any personally identifiable information about you.
How is the information being used?
The information we collect is used to provide the products and services that you have requested or that we think you might have an interest in. It is also used to improve the content of our Web site, to notify you of problems with your requests, or to update you about changes to our Web site.
With whom do we share your information?
In order to operate this Web site and in order to provide you with the products and services you have requested, we occasionally need to share information with third parties. We may transmit your personal information to service providers who assist us in processing orders, shipping products to you, processing your payment information, sending you catalogs, conducting surveys, on and offline sweepstakes, processing job applications, sending you e-mails and newsletters, and helping us decide whether to extend credit to you. We have agreements with these service providers that they will protect your privacy in accordance with our standard Privacy Statement. Some of those organizations may have their own Privacy Statements which may give you additional protections, so you are encouraged to read those statements when presented to you.
How do I access, update, or delete my personally identifiable information?
Due to various legal and recordkeeping requirements, we may be required to maintain records about your purchases or other activities on this website. However, you will always be permitted to opt-out of any marketing uses of information stored about you. If you would like to change your personal information, you may contact us by filling out our Customer Service Contact Form, or by postal mail at:
Blank Shirts, Inc.
1780 Forrest Way
Carson City, NV 89706
What information will be disclosed if required by law?
If required by law, we may provide any and all information we have about you to law enforcement or other government agencies, pursuant to a subpoena, warrant, or other order by a court of competent jurisdiction. In all cases, we will require written documentation of the request, proof of the identity of the law enforcement official making the request, and we will take steps to authenticate the validity of the request. Any law enforcement or government agency request submitted with less than a court-issued order will be evaluated on a case-by-case basis according to the need and urgency, as well as the particular law enforcement agency making the request.
What are cookies and how do we use them?
A cookie is a block of text placed in a file on the user's hard drive by a Web site you've visited. These types of cookies cannot identify an individual user specifically, such as by name or address, unless the cookie data is attached to personally identifiable information such as online registration. BlankShirts.com uses cookies to observe our site visitor's navigation throughout the site. This helps us identify ways to improve the shopping experience.
BlankShirts.com also uses a session cookie, which is a piece of identification between your browser and our server, which helps to do things like keep track of the items in a user's shopping cart, and other information. The shopping cart cookie is saved for a designated period of time in case the users' session expires or they return to complete a purchase within that time frame.
What choices are available to you regarding the collection, use and distribution of the information and how you can correct any inaccuracies in information?
If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by calling, filling out our Customer
Service Contact Form, or by writing to us at the above postal address and telling us that you do not want to receive e-mail from our company.
If you provide us with your e-mail address, you may receive messages about your order status, issues regarding the operations of this Web site, and messages from subsidiaries of Blank Shirts and other companies with operational relationships to Blank Shirts.
If you provide us with your postal address, you may receive periodic catalogs from us, or other notices containing information about new products and services or upcoming events. On occasion, we may make our postal mailing address lists available to subsidiaries and affiliated companies that are part of the Blank Shirts family of companies. We may also make our postal mailing address lists available to other direct mail companies who we believe may have products and services of interest to our customers. However, we do not share e-mail addresses with any outside organizations for marketing purposes. If you do not wish to receive postal mailings from Blank Shirts, its subsidiaries, or third-party organizations, please let us know by calling, filling out our Customer Service Contact Form, or writing to us at the above postal address. Please provide us with your exact name and postal address and state which lists you wish to be removed from so that we can be sure your information is removed from future mailing lists.
We will request your telephone number or facsimile (FAX) number, and if you provide it, you may receive telephone or FAX contact from us with information regarding your orders or requests for information. We do not share phone or FAX numbers with third parties for marketing purposes.
SECURITY
What kind of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control?
Blank Shirts values your business and is committed to doing everything possible to make our online ordering process secure. Any credit card information you enter on our site is strongly encrypted by industry-standard protocol, SSL (Secure Sockets Layer). The Blank Shirts Web site uses SSL to communicate with secure browsers like Firefox, Chrome and Internet Explorer. These browsers encrypt your credit card and personal information in a way that makes it extremely difficult for anyone to intercept and misuse while being transmitted between your computer and our server. Don't worry if your browser is secure or not - if it is insecure, you will not be able to purchase on our online store.
Once you have completed your order online, our security procedures do not end. We take appropriate precautions to protect the security and privacy of the information stored on our computer networks. Our systems are also housed in secure facilities, and access to your data by our employees is limited to a "need to know" basis, controlled by password protected systems, and monitored for abuse.
If you are still unsure of giving your credit card over the Internet, please feel free to phone, fax, or mail your order to us. For telephone ordering or assistance, please call (800) 332-6576. Our fax number for orders is (877) 813-7626. Or, mail your order to:
Blank Shirts, Inc.
1780 Forrest Way
Carson City, NV 89706
If you have any further question regarding your online security, please contact us at (800) 332-6576 or fill out our Customer Service Contact Form.
CHILDREN
In accordance with federal law, we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under age 13 without the verifiable permission of a parent or guardian. If you are under age 13, you are welcome to browse our web site. However you are not permitted to use any of the features of our site that require the collection of any personally identifiable information. If we determine that we have erroneously collected a child's information, we will immediately undertake to delete that data from our records.
GOOGLE
We do use Google AdWords free conversion tracking.
Back to Top
